Unknown: recording the, the thing, but I'm just-
DM: Okay
Unknown: ... recording the video with Eric
DM: 'Cause my recording just stopped.
Unknown: Yeah, you just have to-
DM: Let me restart it
Unknown: All right.
Seeker: Seventh level-
DM: Okay
Seeker: ... chain lightning.
Seeker: That's a,
Seeker: a DC 19 dex save.
DM: Uh, uses a legendary.
Unknown: Nice.
DM: So it takes half damage.
Seeker: Which is?
DM: So roll your damage. So this, okay, so Seeker appears in the puddle of ooze, holds up his glove,
DM: and this burst of thunderous lightning shoots out of his hand, very Limbo-esque, and it strikes the sphere, and the
DM: sphere begins resonating. Roll your damage.
Seeker: That's, uh, 36 divided by two, I guess.
DM: Not divided by two because it's vulnerable to thunder damage.
Seeker: Ah.
DM: So it takes 36 points of damage.
DM: Little cracks start to appear, but not big cracks.
Seeker: And I can bonus action inspiration anybody who's likely to damage it, because they will then do thunder damage.
Delwath: Uh, who's next in the...
Unknown: Uh, Wellby.
DM: Wait. All right, Wellby's next.
Unknown: Oh, you can do thunder damage?
Wellby: If you, can you turn my piercing into thunder?
Unknown: No.
DM: It's just a 1d12 thunder.
Unknown: It's 1d12 extra thunder.
Delwath: I mean, more likely it's probably good to bonus action to give inspiration to somebody who's likely to need the-
DM: Sorry, that was 36 damage you said?
Unknown: Need the saving throw.
Unknown: Yep.
Seeker: Yeah.
Unknown: Whether that's what, I mean-
Wellby: We're both gonna die even if we make the saves though.
Delwath: That's a good point. [laughs]
Unknown: Maybe Kenzo.
Unknown: So maybe just give it to Kenzo.
Unknown: Give it to Kenzo.
Unknown: Our shining hope.
Kenzo: But wait, how, but I can't do thunder damage to-
Delwath: No, no, no. An inspiration's that you can stay up if you have to, if you have to make a save-
Seeker: Oh yeah, yeah
Unknown: ... you can use it.
Seeker: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: I, I'm actually, I mean-
DM: Although the force damage saves
Delwath: ... now I could, I could do thunder damage.
Unknown: I can use a spell.
Seeker: Do it.
Kenzo: Because you can do automatic inspirations, you can do, uh, uh, reaction inspirations, so not your-
Seeker: Is, is that true?
DM: We've been unclear.
DM: No, we've been sort of uncl- It's not really.
Unknown: I mean, sure, whatever.
DM: We've been unclear about it. It's not really the rules.
Unknown: Um-
Seeker: He's 20, he's a 20th level bard.
DM: But-
Seeker: Come on. I'm really inspiring.
DM: It's fine. The reason we stopped is 'cause it's kind of annoying to always be tracking reactions because-
Unknown: Right
DM: ... you know, everybody has a lot of things to do in a reaction.
Unknown: Just use a bonus action to give-
Seeker: That's what I was gonna do, yeah.
DM: No.
Seeker: Give it to one person. I'll give it to
Seeker: Kenzo.
Unknown: Give it to Kenzo.
Delwath: Yeah. Kenzo's good. I mean, yeah, give it to Kenzo.
DM: Uh, it's going to attack you with a pseudopod.
DM: That's a natural 20.
Seeker: Oh God.
Unknown: You'll be fine.
DM: Um-
Unknown: Don't you have like 190 hit points?
Seeker: So I, I removed my temp hit points, so I just-
DM: So you take
DM: tw- uh, 20, 32-
Unknown: You have 190 hit points
DM: ... 33-
Unknown: You're great
DM: ... 36 points of force damage.
DM: Uh,
DM: okay.
Seeker: Guys, I'm really hurt.
Unknown: [laughs]
Seeker: [laughs]
Delwath: Tollen's gonna attack you. [laughs]
DM: Um.
Unknown: Two hours ago.
Kenzo: Do you know what this is like? [laughs]
DM: Wellby is up.
Seeker: I didn't know that, Kenzo.
Unknown: [laughs]
Kenzo: [laughs] This brave, courageous adventurer.
Seeker: Note that I did later dive into the center of the ooze.
Kenzo: You did. You did. You're doing great.
Unknown: You did great.
Delwath: I mean, killing minions is beneficial-
Unknown: Right
Delwath: ... 'cause they can kill you if you don't kill them.
Seeker: Combat is therapy, really.
Unknown: Yeah, it is.
Seeker: It is real.
Unknown: It ki- it kind of is actually.
Unknown: We'll make a save.
Unknown: For Seeker it is.
Unknown: Sure, so, um-
Kenzo: Yeah. So the more bravery you can show in combat, the more healed you are.
Unknown: Okay.
Seeker: Uh.
Unknown: Uh, 9,
Unknown: 20.
DM: Wait, why are you rolling two?
Unknown: I don't know.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [laughs]
Wellby: Actually, because I've been used to rolling two this whole time.
Seeker: Wait, was that a 27 you said?
Wellby: That was a two and a five. Should I just re-
DM: Oh, no, no, the two still hits.
Unknown: Should you just re-roll? [laughs]
Unknown: Two, okay.
DM: So re-roll.
Unknown: Should he just re-roll?
DM: The minions don't have a high AC.
Unknown: Well, I rolled them both at once.
DM: You have a plus 15?
Unknown: With the scare arrows.
DM: Okay, so the minions have a-
Unknown: That's what's sad, is you have a bunch of dice you haven't used
Delwath: ... the minions have a 16 AC.
Unknown: I think I can re-roll, right?
DM: So the two still hits.
Wellby: Awesome. Let's see if I can do more than one.
Unknown: Oh yeah, you can overkill.
Unknown: Are, are you killing minions?
Unknown: Uh, I probably didn't.
Delwath: Wait, what do you get, how do you get sneak attack damage?
Unknown: Oh, fuck.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Shoot these ones.
DM: Shoot those ones, not the ones-
Wellby: That's how I get sneak attack damage.
DM: Yeah. Okay.
Unknown: Indeed.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: [coughs]
Unknown: 24, 32.
DM: Um,
DM: your arrow
DM: strikes this line down.
Delwath: Okay, and so then we have
Unknown: Kenzo.
DM: Uh,
DM: and now a pseudopod
DM: strikes at you.
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Wait, me?
DM: You just hit its minions.
Wellby: I thought maybe it considered them a different thing.
Unknown: Nevermind, just goes down its own.
Unknown: Cast feather fall.
Seeker: It's gonna land again.
DM: 25 points of damage.
Seeker: I need to do-
Unknown: Wait, it strikes me?
DM: Yeah.
Wellby: Did it, it, so it'd be my AC, right?
DM: I rolled a 20.
Seeker: Change its damage type.
DM: I mean, you have a re- you have your reaction back.
Seeker: Oh.
Seeker: That's what Mike was suggesting before.
Unknown: I only have seven hit points, it doesn't matter.
DM: Okay.
Seeker: Yeah.
DM: So you fall.
Wellby: Down goes Wellby again.
Seeker: So what would make it vulnerable to your type of damage?
Kenzo: Make it, make it, turn it into like a thing of, made out of glass.
DM: Yeah.
Seeker: Did Wellby go down again?
DM: Wellby went down again.
Unknown: Yeah.
Unknown: I'll be fine.
Kenzo: [laughs] It, it's my turn now then?
DM: It's, it's Kenzo's turn, yeah.
Unknown: Fuck, it needed to be Seeker's turn.
Unknown: Seeker is last.
Kenzo: No, 'cause Seeker needs to use his int-
Seeker: To turn it to glass
Kenzo: ... to turn, to use as a fucking Limbo, Limbo action to turn the thing into glass so I can fucking kill it.
Seeker: Yeah, so you can just smash it.
Unknown: Yeah.
Seeker: Yeah.
Wellby: How's your int? Can you int it?
Unknown: I can try.
DM: You can try. You might roll it.
DM: It's, it's not a super high DC.
Unknown: I do have bard inspiration.
Unknown: Ah.
Kenzo: I have a 10 intelligence. It's a plus zero.
DM: So you're gonna have to roll d...
DM: But inspiration is, helps a lot-
Unknown: 2d12
DM: ... 'cause it's 2d12, you take the highest And it's only an action, so you can use your haste action to do it.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Unknown: Nice, nice.
Unknown: Yeah, why don't-
Unknown: 'Cause, 'cause right now all these oozes...
Unknown: We can't kill these oozes, right?
Unknown: The minions we can-
DM: They'll just reappear.
Unknown: Yeah.
Wellby: Yeah. Turn it into something that you can damage.
DM: Exactly.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah. That's what I'm saying.
DM: Turn it into glass.
Unknown: I'm, I'm turning them into-
DM: Yeah
Unknown: ... I'm, I'm turning it into glass.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Do that.
Unknown: All right. [sighs] Fuck.
Unknown: Okay. I will do that.
Unknown: All right.
Delwath: Yeah, you're giving Kenzo inspiration.
Unknown: The cosmic roll, right?
DM: It's great.
Kenzo: Okay, so Kenzo goes up and now is, um...
Unknown: You probably-
DM: So you have to move your f- you have to use your full move to get there.
Unknown: That's fine. I have 140 move.
DM: Yeah, I know.
Unknown: Okay.
Unknown: So I get there.
DM: Uh, the minions take an opportunity attack against you.
DM: [paper rustling] Uh, you take-
Unknown: This is your initiative.
DM: You take, uh, [paper rustling] 16 points of piercing damage reduced by half to...
Unknown: Eight.
DM: Eight.
DM: [die thudding]
Unknown: Oh, that's an opportunity attack.
DM: Yeah. [clears throat]
Unknown: Technically I could use my reaction.
DM: No, you could, but I would save it for the ooze attacks.
DM: Although, I don't know, this might work.
DM: Maybe you won't have to face more ooze attacks.
Kenzo: Okay. All right. So now Kenzo
Kenzo: closes his mind, imagines it as a sphere of glass
Unknown: Limbo style.
Kenzo: And what I'm doing, I'm doing an intelligence-
DM: Yep
Kenzo: ... I'm doing an intelligence...
Unknown: Yeah
Unknown: ... super fragile-
Unknown: Focus, focus, focus
Kenzo: ... piece of glass focusing on it.
Unknown: [die rolling]
Unknown: Yeah. [laughs]
DM: Woo. Yeah.
Delwath: He rolled a 20. Yes. [laughs]
Unknown: Oh.
Unknown: Yes.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Well done.
DM: Don't even need to use inspiration.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Oh my God. [laughs]
DM: The
DM: crystal sphere shifts into this fragile glass.
Unknown: Oh.
DM: That was your haste. Go ahead and make your five bludgeoning attacks-
Unknown: Seeker looks over at Kenzo and waves at him
DM: ... that it is now vulnerable to.
Kenzo: Oh my God. All right. So now I, I get, uh-
DM: You get five attacks
Unknown: ... five attacks. Wait.
Unknown: Uh-
DM: And they'll do double damage
Kenzo: ... but two, two staff attacks, three...
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Two staff, three.
Kenzo: Okay. I'll, I'll roll my staff attacks first.
Unknown: Do,
Wellby: do your bonus act- Wait.
Unknown: Are they all regular action?
Unknown: Or any of those bonus actions?
DM: Yeah, the three, three bonus actions.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Three bonus, two-
Unknown: Actually, do your bonus actions first
DM: ... two bonus-
Wellby: 'Cause then you can preserve your action- 'Cause then- ...
Unknown: and then do it for something else ... yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kenzo: Okay. All right. So I'll do my three unarmed strikes first.
Unknown: So each of these is plus three.
Delwath: Wait, you... They can do bludgeoning if you want.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: They don't have to.
Unknown: Okay. [die rolling] Oh, no.
Unknown: Jeez. [laughs]
DM: Uh-
Unknown: Well, it's a, it's a crystal thing.
Kenzo: Hopefully... It's a, it's a piece of cry- Oh, I fucking rolled a one.
DM: That one doesn't hit.
Unknown: But 18-
DM: What do you have to hit plus?
Unknown: 18, 16, plus 13.
DM: Uh, 18 hits.
Unknown: Does, does-
DM: 16 misses.
Unknown: Uh, you could bardic that.
DM: Oh, yeah. You could bardic that.
DM: That's very close.
DM: Um-
Wellby: How much damage do you do with this?
Unknown: 'Cause you still have to roll damage
Kenzo: ... let me, let me roll damage on the first, the first one that hits.
Unknown: See how it goes.
Unknown: Yeah. [die rolling] So that is...
Kenzo: Okay, so that's not bad. That's 13 damage
Unknown: for the first one.
Kenzo: I'm gonna, I'm gonna roll my other staff attacks.
Unknown: Yeah, okay. Yeah. Sure.
Kenzo: Okay. So now I get two staff attacks.
Unknown: Two staffs, yeah.
Unknown: Right, yeah. Two staff attacks.
DM: There's big cracks showing up on it.
DM: [die rolling]
Kenzo: Fuck. Oh, these are 15 though, so 20 and 21.
DM: Yeah, that hits.
Unknown: Okay. So-
Delwath: Oh, and then 3d 12.
Unknown: 3d 12.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: Plus 18.
Unknown: 3d 12 plus 18.
Kenzo: [die rolling] Oh, this is... Okay.
Unknown: 17 and 18.
DM: 17 and 18.
Unknown: 35?
DM: 35 plu- 35 plus 18 or just 35?
Unknown: Total of 35.
DM: Uh, hold on.
DM: Oh, no. Okay. So Kenzo hits this once,
DM: cracks appear.
DM: Hits it twice,
DM: cracks appear. Hits it the third time and you smash right through it.
Unknown: Yes.
DM: Uh,
DM: how far away is Wellby from the edge?
Unknown: Do I, why, why does it matter how far away I is?
Unknown: The edge of what?
DM: The ooze. Pretty close, right?
DM: How far away is Delwath?
Unknown: At max move away.
DM: Okay.
Delwath: So, uh, like 70 feet or something, 70 or 80 feet.
Unknown: Seeker is right there.
DM: Okay. Um-
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: The, the m- ooze matter begins, like, rushing in in this implosion and it hits
DM: Kenzo and
DM: Seeker in the middle.
DM: You both take 21 points of force damage
DM: and are tossed 1,000 feet into the air.
Unknown: Oh my God. [laughs]
DM: Uh-
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Wellby, uh, you fail one death save.
DM: You are out of range.
DM: Nothing happens to you.
Unknown: 21 damage.
DM: So that's-
Unknown: 1,000 feet
DM: ... 20d6 falling damage.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: But you don't...
Kenzo: I mean, I'm a natural being and I can fly, whatever.
Unknown: It's all, it's all fine.
DM: Right. So you take no flying damage.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It doesn't matter to you.
Seeker: Uh, I'm gonna have to do something about this.
Unknown: [tapping keyboard]
Kenzo: Oh, yeah. You don't wanna, you don't, you don't wanna fall 1,000 feet.
Unknown: No, that might be, that might be painful.
DM: It's 20d6 damage.
Delwath: But you could possibly do something.
Unknown: Who's, what, what's...
Unknown: That was Kenzo's turn.
Unknown: Uh-
Unknown: Oh, it would be the oozes's turn.
DM: It's-
Unknown: It's gonna take, like, two rounds for you to get back down there
DM: ... it's now solidifying into crystal-
Unknown: Right. I see
DM: ... all across.
Unknown: There's plenty of time to cast something.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: No, it's dead.
Wellby: Yes. No, I'm saying falling 10,000 feet or 1,000 feet- 1,000 feet ...
Unknown: is gonna take, like, 12 seconds.
DM: You fall 500 feet a round.
Unknown: Feet a s-
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah.
DM: So you have time to cast something.
Unknown: [laughs]
Delwath: You use your scroll of wish to cast feather fall.
DM: Don't actually do that.
DM: [laughs]
Unknown: Funny anyway.
Wellby: Okay. Can we run down and grab you?
Kenzo: Uh, can I step with the wind to pick him up?
DM: Uh-
Unknown: I can-
DM: No, because he falls f- You're, you're just, like, la-di-da, floating.
Unknown: No, but I can fly.
DM: I know, but you can't fly 500 feet in a round.
Kenzo: I'm, I'm, I'm, I have... Oh, I'm, I'm hast-
DM: He's falling 500 feet down.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: You'd have to catch him 500 feet down, and you can't get that far.
Unknown: What's your movement?
Unknown: 140.
DM: Uh, wait.
Unknown: On haste.
Delwath: So hold on. So you, so that's three.
Unknown: You have to push him that way.
DM: You can't get quite there.
Unknown: Oh, oh, oh, hold on, hold on. I can just-
DM: Whose turn is next?
Seeker: ... animate- The ladder [laughing] and hold on to
Delwath: it as we fly down. I was gonna, I was gonna...
Delwath: I had a plan, but this is a much better plan.
Unknown: [laughs] Dramatically better.
Seeker: I knew the ladder was gonna play a role.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: So, so as the, as the force of this Limbo explosion destroying the heart of the Ooze crystallizes this shell of
DM: matter across the battlefield, um,
DM: Seeker, you all see, except Wellby, who's unconscious, but hears the story later.
Delwath: No, I'm, I'm, I'm waking Wellby up.
Unknown: [laughs] I...
Delwath: No, wait, Wellby's gonna be conscious.
DM: Oh, 'cause it's Delwath's turn.
Unknown: I get a turn.
DM: Yeah, yeah.
Unknown: I'm not messing around anymore.
Unknown: 34.
DM: Okay.
Unknown: Points? Yeah. You hit?
Unknown: Oh, wow.
DM: So Wellby turns around-
Unknown: [laughs] What the hell are they doing up there?
DM: ...
DM: and sees, sees Seeker madly, like scrambling to pull the ladder off of his like belt or wherever you keep it, strapped to your backpack.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And then just like m- muttering something, and suddenly you see the ladder
DM: flying.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: A faint image of a superhero cape streaming behind it as it wraps around Seeker, grabs him, and slowly
DM: and gently brings him down to the ground, preventing him from being squashed flat by 1,000 foot fall.
Kenzo: E clu so we may rise.
Unknown: Yes.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: And then you turn and look at each other.
DM: The Ooze dead.
Unknown: Are the minions gone?
DM: The minions are t- turned into solid crystal.
Unknown: Crystal. Yeah. All right.
DM: They're everything turned into...
Unknown: Oh, my God. Oh.
DM: And you look as you see the ash slowly beginning to settle from the sky around you.
Kenzo: Put the cape down now. Phew.
DM: So stressful. Gotta add a few more.
Unknown: Kenzo's really the hero of that combat.
Delwath: You gotta get a few more- [laughs] ...
Kenzo: a few more little leaves on your tree there.
Unknown: [laughs]
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: And so you turn and you look at each other.
DM: Seeker's probably scraping some crystal off the ground.
Unknown: Oh, yes.
DM: Uh,
DM: and now what?
DM: Contact the rangers?
Unknown: Yeah, we gotta get the Heartroot, right?
Unknown: Where's the Heartroot gonna go?
Unknown: In the river? Right here.
Unknown: I think the cistern.
DM: Put, put it back in the cistern where it came from.
Unknown: Yeah, yeah,
Kenzo: yeah. Yeah. Let's, uh, contact the rangers.
Unknown: Let's teleport over when we're ready.
Unknown: Do you have
Unknown: a seventh level spell slot left?
Delwath: Um. You have a seventh and an eighth, right?
Unknown: I think I have.
DM: Yeah, 'cause Seeker was shape changed for almost the whole combat.
Unknown: It was casting spells.
DM: Shape change turned out to be quite a fun spell to have.
Wellby: Seventh. If you have a seventh and an eighth, we can go pick it up and come right back.
Seeker: Yeah, exactly. I, I, um, I burned my seventh.
DM: Ow.
Unknown: So I'm-
DM: Unchain lightning
Unknown: ... I just have a eighth
Unknown: now.
DM: Well, it's not gonna kill you to teleport to Aurbez, take a long rest, and then teleport back.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: It might be good, actually.
Seeker: Yeah, I'm pretty spent.
DM: So over the course of the day
DM: you teleport back to Aurbez and-
Wellby: Can we roll the teleport percent just to-
DM: Oh, yeah, yeah. Just roll
Unknown: ... to see what happens?
DM: Just see what happens.
Delwath: Just for the sake of curiosity. Don't you auto succeed, 'cause you have the dirt from-
DM: He has the dirt. That's true, he has the dirt.
Unknown: So is it 100%?
DM: Yeah, it's guaranteed if you,
DM: um-
Unknown: Sover. No.
Unknown: I'm just too good at this.
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: [laughs]
DM: Uh-
Delwath: I mean, you took some of the dirt from here too, right?
Unknown: Yeah
DM: ... you explain what happened to g- to great, um, excitement in Aurbez.
DM: Talk to Catiline Malras and some other rangers,
DM: and then after you've had a chance to rest
DM: and
DM: recover a little bit and, you know, maybe communicate with Phaldrik and tell him to meet you at Isengai, which he was already planning on doing, um,
DM: you carefully, um,
DM: like you and Sever... How many...
DM: Oh, you can just teleport an object.
Unknown: Right.
DM: But Kenzo counts as part of the Heartroot.
DM: So I'm gonna say you can teleport Kenzo and the Heartroot together.
Unknown: Oh, o- okay.
DM: Um,
DM: and then you can just use a second teleport to tel- 'cause you have two seventh level slots now.
Delwath: I mean, you have to do
Delwath: three to go back and forth, but that's okay.
DM: No, you're, you're resting in Aurbez.
Unknown: Yeah.
DM: So you're gonna end up in Isengai, but then your shard is in Isengai.
Unknown: Right.
DM: So you don't have to teleport back to Aurbez.
Delwath: I just meant if he was gonna teleport to get us as well.
DM: No, if you teleport an object, you don't have to go-
Unknown: Oh
DM: ... you don't have to go with it.
Unknown: Yeah. Yeah.
DM: So you teleport
DM: Kenzo and the Heartroot
DM: back to the cistern.
DM: That, that, that is right there, that's Kenzo and the Heartroot.
Unknown: There you go. There it is.
DM: And Kenzo begins to like gradually start to like
DM: f- you know, settle it back into the, the water.
DM: Um, you know,
DM: take your staff and like knock down some rubble and stuff to make a, a path so that some of the river can flow in, and it can start to decontaminate the river from the long influence of
DM: Limbo.
DM: And the-
Kenzo: It's like Charlie Brown's Christmas tree
DM: ... and the rangers, some of the rangers and you, you can teleport up to eight.
Unknown: Eight.
DM: Right? So you bring the three of you and-
Unknown: Five
DM: ... five rangers to sort of help start to get things settled.
DM: Spend a couple of days in Isingue making sure the Heartroot is safe.
Kenzo: What- what's the Heartroot... Once the Heartroot get...
Kenzo: Like, what happens once the Heartroot gets-
DM: So it begins to... It, like, stretches out and it, like, expands.
DM: And,
DM: you know, Kenzo's a- attuned to it, right, and pretty connected, so there's this
DM: massive sigh of relief.
DM: And then it's almost like it begins to drop these little filaments into the river, and as the water flows past, it's like it's decontaminating the
DM: ash and everything that fell from, from Limbo in the river.
DM: It's gonna take a while to, like, rebuild the cistern.
Unknown: Right.
DM: There's some manual labor that needs to happen before it can really
DM: go back, but it's reconnected to the river and sort of...
DM: And it finds it immediate- You actually see it immediately, the, like, filamentous roots just immediately tunnel through the little gaps so it can reach out and grab the river
DM: water. And water starts, like, flowing in, back into the cistern along the channels that it carves through the rubble, sort of feeling its way out to
DM: reconstruct the,
DM: um,
DM: reconstruct the, the patterns and flows and channels that once were there long ago.
DM: And actually, as you're here, you get the feeling that the cistern was here even before the city.
Unknown: Hmm.
DM: And the city,
DM: it, like, the Heartroot is actually beginning to grow new pillars that-
Kenzo: Did we, did we mirror the Heartroot?
Unknown: We did, right?
DM: Yeah.
Unknown: Yeah. Okay.
DM: That's when you saw it, like, getting created-
DM: It's like from before time
DM: ... from before time.
Unknown: From before time.
Kenzo: Right, right. We should, we should mirror the cistern too.
Unknown: There's something in the cistern.
DM: I wanna, I wanna see the, uh,
DM: the queen of-
Kenzo: Oh, yeah, yeah. For sure. We'll do that one too.
DM: So-
Unknown: We got a bunch. We got, we got time
DM: ... yeah. So time passes,
DM: the
DM: Heartroot settles into place.
DM: Um,
DM: more rangers start to come, um,
DM: you know, over the course of a, of, of a week or two.
DM: Um, you establish a little bit of a camp at Isingue.
DM: There's still dangers in the wild, but nothing that, you know, is particularly challenging for a
DM: group of such adventurers.
DM: And
DM: you remain over the course of
DM: a couple weeks until
DM: sometime in October, early October.
DM: Things seem stable here,
DM: and you find yourself now back on Vindasharna wondering what you're gonna do next.
DM: And in that time you can of course look at, you know, three things in the mirror,
DM: and there's some time while Vindasharna flies to drop the monks off and other people off wherever you want to be dropped off.
Unknown: Oh, yeah, we found the monks.
DM: Mm-hmm.
Seeker: So the monks kind of missed 30 years of
Unknown: local history.
DM: Yep.
Unknown: Mm-hmm.
Unknown: Um,
Unknown: I gotta use the bathroom.
Unknown: Should we, like, sh- should we, like-
DM: Yeah, let's move over there
Unknown: ... shift, shift over to the...
Unknown: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Seeker: That was pretty bonkers.
Unknown: That was amazing